

Arman AjabkhaniSENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - JAVA

PROFILE

Gender: Male

Nationality: Iranian Birth Date: 8/25/1983

Software engineer with a strong background in design and development on

Java platform.

Keen learner and problem solver with a passion for algorithms, architecture. Highly experienced in developing financial, payment and banking systems with SOA and micro-services architecture.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science from Sheikh Bahaee Isfahan University in Software Engineering from September 2000 to September 2006.

LANGUAGES

English

Persian

CONTACT

Email: arm.khani@gmail.com

Mobile: +98 912 8589 456

LinkedIn: Arman Ajabkhani's profile Address: No. 23, Parastoo2 Alley, Kaj St., Taherkhani St., Tehran, Iran

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sava Arman Kish (Bitex)

Senior Java Developer

Nov 2018 - Present

- I currently work as senior java developer of the exchange project.
- I developed reactive java using RxJava and Vert.x and Swagger.
- I design and implement feature in user-account and notification.
- I design and developed a few micro-services.

TOSAN (Payment and Banking solution provider)

Team Tech Head

Mar 2017 - Nov 2018

- Mentoring, coaching, training and planning tasks for the team members.
- Analysis, Design, Development, Deployment and Maintenance several applications and micro-services.
- Designing and developing some complicated features in open banking API.

TOSAN (Payment and Banking solution provider)

Junior / Senior Java Developer

Nov 2011 - Mar 2017

- I worked as a member of the Channel Manger(CM) team.
- I developed functionalities for tracking and authentication and authorization.
- I developed and implemented Web Services with JAX-WS.
- I implemented many feature in Persistence layer using Hibernate
- I had Extensive experience using framework APIs like spring and Hibernate.

Elm o Sanat

Senior C#/ASP.NET Developer

Sep 2010 – Oct 2011

- I implement several new features in the School product.
- I used Entity Framework in school product and custom report generator.
- I implement virtual replication on SQL Server with use web service.

Netbina (Online Advertising)

Junior C#/ASP.NET Developer

October 2006 - March 2009

- I implemented several functionalities for the advertising products.
- I work on developing a Blog Service with C# and ASP.NET.



Arman Ajabkhani SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - JAVA

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Core Java 8	Spring
Design Patterns	Spring Boot
SOA	Spring MVC / AOP
Microservices	Spring Batch
Event Driven Architecture	Spring Security
Software Architecture Patterns	Spring Data / JPA
Apache Tomcat	Hibernate
Live Migration	Spring AOP / aspectj
Concurrent Programming	Vert.x
Reactive Programming	Redis / Hazelcast
RESTful Web Services	Oracle PL/SQL Development
SOAP / JAX-WS /JAX-RS	Gradle / Maven
Docker and Docker Compose	Git / Subversion / TFS
CI / CD	Jira / TFS / HP ALM
Jenkins /	Test Driven Development
Swagger	JUnit / TestNg/Power Mock / Mockito
Apache Kafka / ActiveMQ	UML / Agile and RUP Methodologies
OAuth / JWT	CORE Banking / Payment Systems
HTML / CSS / javascript	Confluence / SharePoint / Documenting
C# 4.5/ ASP.NET	Crypto Currency Exchanges
Entity Framework/ WCF	Block Chain / Hyperledger Fabric